Guide to the United Student Christian Council Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- USCC Correspondence, Series II
  - Ruth Wick (Executive Secretary 1952-54)
    - Rossman, Parker, 1955-1954 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Stringfellow, William, 1952-1954 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - USCC Chairman: Scott Jones and William Metcalf, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - USCC Chairman of Executive Committee: Bryant Drake, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - USCC Vice Chairman: Herbert Donovan, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Herluf Jensen (Executive Secretary 1954-59)
    - A, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - African Medical Student Fund, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Anderson, Scott, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Concerning Application of African American undergraduates to University of North Carolina, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - B, 1956-1959 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Baly, Dennis, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - re. Bible Study Citizens of God's Kingdom by Roger Shinn, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Burry, Alan, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - C, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Converse, Paul, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - D, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Deschner, John, 1954-1958 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Concerning D.T. Nile's May Visitation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - E, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Ecumenical Drama Caravan Team, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - F, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Flory, Margaret, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Foreign Student Scholarship, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - G, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - H, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Huntwork, Dorothy, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - I-J, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Inter-Office, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Invitations to Speak, 1956-1958 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Inquiries, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Jensen: Personal and Miscellaneous, 1955-1959 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Jothiratnam, A., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - K, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Knopf, Gerald E., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Kutztown Publishing Company, 1955-1958 (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - L, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Letter to John Foster Dulles re. Protestant Persecution in Columbia, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Lutheran Student Association of American and National Lutheran Council, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - M, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - Maury, Philippe, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - Michael Press, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Morrison, Martha, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - N-O, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - re. National Canterbury Study Conference at Colorado Springs, CO, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - re. New York State Staff Conference, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Otterness, Alice, 1955, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - P, 1955-1959 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Personnel, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Publicity and Promotional Material incl. Pat Miller's (USCC student Vice Chairman) appearance on College Press Conference television show in which he challenged Senator Herman Tallmadge on the civil rights issue. Photograph included., 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Q-R, 1954-1959 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Rossman, Parker, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - S, 1955-1959 (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - re. Speaking engagement at Tri-College Conference, Buffalo, New York, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - Stowe, David, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Stringfellow, William, 1953-1958 (Box 12, Folder 156)
    - T, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Travel: Jensen's Trip to Iceland, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - Travel: Jensens' visits to various universities, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Travel: Jensen's visit to the west coast, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - Travel: WSCF Day of Prayer at Syracuse University, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - U-V, 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - USCC Chairman: David Willis, Norman Hjelm, and Paul Schrading, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - USCC Chairman of Executive Committee: Hart Helmich, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - USCC Ex-Officio Officers, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - USCC Officers, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - USCC Officers, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - W, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Wick, Ruth, 1954-1958 (Box 13, Folder 167)
    - Wiley, David includes report on travel to the Soviet Union, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 168)
    - X-Z, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 169)
    - Zabriske, Philip, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 170)
- USCC Committees and Commissions, Series III
  - Budget and Finance Committee
    - Committee Records
      - Audits, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 171)
      - CORE budget, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 172)
      - CORE budget, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 173)
      - CORE budget, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 174)
      - Critical ratios revision, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 175)
      - Critical ratios returns, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 176)
      - Critical ratios, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 177)
      - Financial summary, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 178)
      - Income and expenditure statements, 1945-1950 (Box 13, Folder 179)
      - Income and expenditure statements, 1955, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 180)
      - Memos, 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 181)
      - Minutes, 1947-1957 (Box 14, Folder 182)
      - Proposed budget, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 183)
      - Pledges, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 184)
      - Working paper no. 1 and notes, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 185)
      - WSCF finance reports, 1944-1951 (Box 14, Folder 186)
      - WSCF finance reports, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 187)
      - WSCF finance reports includes operating budget, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 188)
      - WSCF finance statements includes (removed from binder), 1949-1951 (Box 161, Folder 1850)
      - WSCF operating account, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 1851)
    - Correspondence
      - Niebuhr, Ursula includes handwritten statements of income and expenditures, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 189)
      - Contributions (Kept as an example. The rest have been discarded), 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 190)
      - Mackie, Robert re. WSCF finances, 1945-1947 (Box 15, Folder 191)
      - General, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 192)
      - General, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 193)
      - Prospective contributors, 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 194)
      - Fund raising appeals to the Foreign Mission Conference, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 1852)
      - Approaches to foundations and individual, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 195)
      - Contributors, 1948-1951 (Box 15, Folder 196)
      - WSCF financing for projects, 1948-1950 (Box 161, Folder 1853)
      - Prospective contributors re. university chapels, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 197)
      - Maury, Philippe re. WSCF finances, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 198)
      - WSCF contributions, 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 199)
      - Board Appropriations, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 200)
      - Proctor and Gamble stock, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 201)
      - re. Search for treasurer, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 202)
      - Appeals--USA movements, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 203)
      - Maury, Philippe re. WSCF finances, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 204)
      - Foundations approached for funding, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 205)
      - General, 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 206)
      - Prospective contributors, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 207)
      - General, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 208)
      - Prospective contributors, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 209)
      - Appeals: The Phelp-Stokes Fund, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 210)
      - Acknowledgment of contributions, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - NCCC-USCC Merger
      - Correspondence, re. budget procedures includes source of income reports, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 212)
      - Correspondence, re. coordinating finances with NCCC, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      - Correspondence, re. financial matters relating to the USCC NCCC merger, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 214)
      - Correspondence, re. USCC income and expenditures, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 215)
      - Construction of 1956 budgets, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 216)
      - NCCC income and expenditures, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 217)
  - Campus Strategy Committee
    - Committee Records
      - Campus Strategy budget, 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 218)
      - Budget information sheets, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 219)
      - Campus Strategy workbook includes drafts and planning information, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 220)
      - Correspondence, General, 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 221)
      - Correspondence, General, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 222)
      - Correspondence, re. Campus Strategy workbook, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 223)
      - Correspondence, Personnel, 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 224)
      - Correspondence, General, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 225)
      - Memos, 1948-1952 (Box 18, Folder 226)
      - Minutes, 1948-1952 (Box 18, Folder 227)
      - Reports: Cooperative projects on college campuses, 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 228)
      - Reports: Visits to individual campuses, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 229)
      - Survey results, 1948, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 230)
    - University and College Campus Cooperative Student Work
      - Alabama State, Albany, New York, Albion College, Alton memorial School of Nursing, Amherst College, and Andover-Newton Seminary, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 231)
      - Atlanta, Georgia, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 232)
      - Arizona State University and Bellingham, Washington, 1946, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 233)
      - Boston University, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 234)
      - Bowling Green State University: brochures and newsletters, 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 235)
      - Bowling Green State University: correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 236)
      - Bowling Green State University: reports, 1948-1952 (Box 19, Folder 237)
      - Brooklyn College and Bucknell University, 1948-1951 (Box 19, Folder 238)
      - Champlain College, Chicago Teacher's College, Cleveland, and Colorado State, 1948-1952 (Box 19, Folder 239)
      - College of Buffalo, 1948-1950 (Box 19, Folder 240)
      - College of Buffalo, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 241)
      - Connecticut and Cornell College, Iowa, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 242)
      - Cornell University, Ithaca, New York, 1945-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 243)
      - Cortland State Teachers College, 1948-1951 (Box 19, Folder 244)
      - Duke University, 1949-1950 (Box 19, Folder 245)
      - Elmhurst College, Fargo, ND, Farragut, ID, and Freedonia, NY, 1948-1951 (Box 19, Folder 246)
      - Fresno, CA, Garrett Biblical Institute, Georgia Student Christian Council, Glennville, W.VA, and Green Mountain Junior College, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 247)
      - Hampton Institute, 1946-1950 (Box 20, Folder 248)
      - Hartwick College, Illinois College, Indiana University, Indiana region, and Indiana State Teachers College, 1947-1952 (Box 20, Folder 249)
      - Iowa, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 250)
      - Kalamazoo College and Kansas State, 1949-1952 (Box 20, Folder 251)
      - Kent State University, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 252)
      - Louisiana State University, Macalester College, Maryville College, and Miami University, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 253)
      - Michigan region, 1948-1952 (Box 20, Folder 254)
      - Michigan State College, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 255)
      - Michigan State College, 1950-1952 (Box 21, Folder 256)
      - Mohawk College, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 257)
      - Montana State College, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 258)
      - Montana State University, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 259)
      - Nashville and North Carolina, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 260)
      - New York Metropolitan area, 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 261)
      - Oakland, CA and Oberlin College, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 262)
      - Ohio region, 1947-1950 (Box 21, Folder 263)
      - Ohio State University, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 264)
      - Oklahoma A&M, Oneonta, NY, Pacific University, Plattsburg, NY, and Pottsdam, NY, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 265)
      - Princeton, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 266)
      - Pullman, WA, Queens and Nassau sCm, Rhode Island State College, and Ripon College, 1948-1952 (Box 22, Folder 267)
      - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1950-1952 (Box 22, Folder 268)
      - Rutgers University, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 269)
      - Sampson College, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 270)
      - San Jose State College, 1947-1951 (Box 22, Folder 271)
      - South Carolina, Stanford University, State College of New Mexico, State College, PA, Susquehanna University, and Syracuse University, 1947-1952 (Box 22, Folder 272)
      - Southern Illinois University, 1947-1950 (Box 22, Folder 272)
      - Southern Illinois University, 1950-1952 (Box 22, Folder 273)
      - Tallahassee, FL, Tempe, AZ, Temple University, Texas, Texas Christian University, and Tucson, AZ, 1948-1952 (Box 22, Folder 274)
      - Union Theological Seminary, University of Alabama, and University of Arizona, 1949-1951 (Box 22, Folder 275)
      - University of Boston and University of California, 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 276)
      - University of Chicago, 1947-1951 (Box 23, Folder 277)
      - University of Cincinnati and University of Georgia, 1949-1951 (Box 23, Folder 278)
      - University of Idaho, 1948-1952 (Box 23, Folder 279)
      - University of Illinois, University of Iowa, University of Kansas, and University of Kentucky, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 278)
      - University of Maryland, 1950-1952 (Box 23, Folder 279)
      - University of Michigan, 1947-1949 (Box 23, Folder 280)
      - University of Minnesota, 1949-1952 (Box 23, Folder 281)
      - University of Missouri, University of Nebraska, and University of Nevada, 1948-1951 (Box 25, Folder 282)
      - University of New Hampshire, 1947-1951 (Box 25, Folder 283)
      - University of New Mexico, 1948-1952 (Box 25, Folder 284)
      - University of North Carolina, University of Oklahoma, University of Oregon, University of Pennsylvania, University of Pittsburgh, University of Rochester, University of South Carolina, and University of South Carolina, 1947-1952 (Box 25, Folder 285)
      - University of Texas, 1946-1951 (Box 25, Folder 286)
      - University of Toledo, 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 287)
      - University of Utah, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 288)
      - University of Utah, 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 289)
      - University of Washington, University of Wisconsin, Upper Iowa University, and Upsala College, 1947-1952 (Box 26, Folder 290)
      - USCC of Southern California, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 291)
      - Vincennes University, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, and Wagner College, 1948-1951 (Box 26, Folder 292)
      - Washington D.C. region, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 293)
      - Washington and Lee University and Wayne University, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 294)
      - Western Illinois State College, 1947-1949 (Box 26, Folder 295)
      - Western Illinois State College, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 296)
      - Western Illinois State College, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 297)
      - West Virginia Wesleyan and Willow Run, Michigan, 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 298)
      - Yale University, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 299)
      - Youngstown College and Ypsilanti, Michigan, 1946, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 300)
  - Committee on Ecumenical Volunteer Service Projects
    - Carbon copies from Joseph Howell, Associate Executive Secretary for Congregational Christian Service Committee and Secretary for Ecumenical Work Camps, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 301)
    - Circular Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 302)
    - Commission on Youth Service Projects Executive Committee Minutes and Invest Your Summer 1955, 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 303)
    - Correspondence, re. Finance and budget matters, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 304)
    - Correspondence, Howell, Joseph, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 305)
    - Correspondence, re. Ecumenical Work Camps, 1955-56 (Box 27, Folder 306)
    - Correspondence, re. Service Projects, 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 307)
    - Correspondence, re. Voluntary Service meeting in India, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 308)
    - Correspondence, re. Russian/American exchange program, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 309)
    - Formation of committee including consultations on ecumenical work camps, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 310)
    - High School exchange program, Brethren Service Commission, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 311)
    - Information on various work camps including brochures and reports, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - Memos, 1954-1958 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - Minutes, 1955-1958 (Box 27, Folder 314)
    - Program Operations Committee includes memos and minutes, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 315)
    - Report concerning program for Soviet students in USA, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Executive Committee
    - Committee Records
      - Address by Herluf Jensen to the Executive Committee, November 26-28, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 317)
      - Arrangements, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 318)
      - Bank account signature authorization vote, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 319)
      - Directory, 1945-1958 (Box 28, Folder 320)
      - Ecumenical arrangements, 1952-1953 (Box 28, Folder 321)
      - Employing an executive secretary, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 322)
      - Field representative proposal, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 323)
      - Jensen's notes on Executive Committee meeting, May 3-5, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 324)
      - Maps of member movements for coordinating consultations, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 325)
      - Memos, 1946-1958 (Box 28, Folder 326)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1958 (Box 28, Folder 327)
      - Officer's meeting, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 328)
      - Possible ecumenical magazine, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 329)
      - Proposed Christianity and the Arts Conference/Festival research materials, circa 1950s (Box 160, Folder 1839)
      - Study of the member movements, Spring 1947 (Box 29, Folder 330)
      - Tentative calendars, 1947, 1951, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 331)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1944-1947 (Box 29, Folder 332)
      - Goddykoontz, Harry, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 333)
      - Member movement resolutions, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 334)
      - Political issues, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 335)
      - General, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 336)
      - Moore, Tom, 1948-49 (Box 29, Folder 337)
      - re. By law revision, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Corresponding members, 1949-1950 (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - McCaw, John, 1949-50 (Box 29, Folder 340)
      - General, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 341)
      - Proposed Christianity and the Arts Conference/Festival, 1952, 1955 (Box 160, Folder 1840)
      - General, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 342)
      - General, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 343)
      - re. Possible change in conference cycle, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 344)
      - General, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 345)
    - Meeting Agendas, Minutes and Reports
      - 1500s and 500s report, 1946-1947 (Box 30, Folder 346)
      - Forces at work on the college campus, n.d (Box 30, Folder 347)
      - Kalamazoo proposals, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 348)
      - Meeting agenda, February 13-15, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 349)
      - Meeting agenda, May 1-3, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 350)
      - Meeting agendas, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 351)
      - Meeting agendas, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 352)
      - Meeting agendas, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 353)
      - Meeting agendas, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 354)
      - Meeting agendas, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 355)
      - Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 356)
      - Minutes, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 357)
      - Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 358)
      - Minutes, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 359)
      - Minutes, 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 360)
      - Minutes, February 14, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 361)
      - Minutes, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 362)
      - Minutes, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 363)
      - Minutes, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 364)
      - Minutes, 1957-1959 (Box 32, Folder 365)
      - Miscellaneous reports, 1946-1957 (Box 32, Folder 366)
      - Preliminary report on regional ecumenical work, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 367)
      - Preparatory papers for executive committee meeting, May 5-7, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 368)
      - Preparatory papers for executive committee meeting, March, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Proposal reports and papers to executive committee, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 370)
      - Quadrennial reports, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 371)
      - Recommendations from Personnel committee to the Executive committee, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 372)
      - SCMs and the [Korean War] Emergency, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 373)
      - Small Colleges Proposals, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 374)
      - Report on Student Industry Camp in Ontario, Canada, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 375)
      - Summary discussion of the USCC and UCYM on Question "What is the Task of the Christian Youth?", 1950 (Box 33, Folder 376)
      - Working Papers I-IX, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - Study Department
    - Bible Study Training conference information, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 378)
    - Catalogs, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 379)
    - Circulars, 1949-1958 (Box 33, Folder 380)
    - Committee membership, 1951-1953 (Box 33, Folder 381)
    - Bibliography of Comprehensive Student Work and Bibliography of Religion in Higher Education, 1951, circa 1952 (Box 33, Folder 382)
    - Consultation on the Racial Question, May 23, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 383)
    - Correspondence, re. Subscription information, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 384)
    - Correspondence, re. Requests for the grey book Christians in World Struggle, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 385)
    - Correspondence, re. Faculty Consultation, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 386)
    - Correspondence, General, 1951, 1955-1956, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 387)
    - Correspondence, re. Bible Study Guide Jeremiah, 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 388)
    - Correspondence, re. Bible Study Guide Colleges and Universities--Yesterday and Today, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 389)
    - Correspondence, re. Reprinting of M.A. Thomas's Musings in the Secret Place, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 390)
    - The Death of Jesus Christ: a Bible Study on What Led Christians to Study the Bible prepared by Paul Lehmann, August 1951 (Box 34, Folder 391)
    - Draft, Ecumenical Conversations for Students including criticism and research material, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 392)
    - Draft, Raising Basic Questions about the University (Pilot Study Guide), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 393)
    - Draft, Study on a Weekend by J. Robert Nelson includes correspondence and I am God and Not Man: a Study Guide on the Book of the Prophet Hosea by William Hamilton, 1953, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 394)
    - Evangelization of the University, 1948-1951 (Box 34, Folder 395)
    - Evangelization of the University, 1948-1951 (Box 34, Folder 396)
    - Faculty Consultation: Meeting Agendas, Minutes, and Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 397)
    - Finances, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 398)
    - Group Study Questionnaire, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 399)
    - Inventory, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 400)
    - Literature Requests, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 401)
    - Memos, 1951-1958 (Box 35, Folder 402)
    - Minutes, 1951-1956 (Box 35, Folder 403)
    - Minutes, 1956-1958 (Box 35, Folder 404)
    - Nominations to the Committee, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 405)
    - Paper, Church, World and Vocation by Thomas Wieser (Box 35, Folder 406)
    - Paper, From a Geography of Mission to a Life of Mission, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 407)
    - Papers, The Psychological and Spiritual Mood of the Campus, A Theology and Strategy for Campus Evangelism, You Can See it Now by Harry Smith (Box 35, Folder 408)
    - Pamphlet, The Bible the Church the Student Christian Movement by Harvey Cox includes revised manuscript, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 409)
    - Pamphlet, Christ in You: a Study Guide for Paul's Letter to the Colossians includes outline and drafts (Box 35, Folder 410)
    - Pamphlet, Colleges and Universities-Yesterday and Today (Study Guide for the Pilot Study), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 411)
    - Pamphlet, Witness to the Truth including draft and criticisms, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 412)